Ladies and gentlemen, what a great honor for me this evening to end up at the
Cleveland Hall of Fame.
Amen for all seasons. Arnie de la Porte.
I know as we go through our life's journey, we meet various people, such as As
others we see sometimes, but others leave an everlasting memory.
I, as an entrepreneur many years ago, met this evening's inductee, and I was
introduced to him as a man of the
romantic network contacts, and then I find out that all of his contacts are his
friends, and you wonder how is all that
possible? Yes, it's not easy. Only a few people walk the walk that Arnie de la
Porte walked.
He had many accomplishments. His life vision was to help others. He had many
dreams. His biggest dream was to have the
Cleveland Port as the best container port in the Great Lakes. His other dream
was to build Cleveland as a big
international community, and many, many others. He loved his homeland, the
Netherlands. He served as an honorary
consul for the Netherlands. He was an active member of the Cleveland Rotary
Club, the Cuyahoga County
Senea Railroad International Business Network, I can just go on and on and on.
This evening, I applaud Arnie de la Porte, a
man whose footsteps are left for us to continue his walk here in the city of
Cleveland, and I congratulate his son who
will be receiving the award.